(Howard:)His name is Buttons.
(Howard:)Anyway, if you had
your own game character...
(Howard:)...we could hang out,
maybe go on a quest.
- That sounds interesting.
- So you'll think about it?
(Penny:)Oh, I don't think
I'll be able to stop thinking about it.
(Raj:)Smooth.
- We're home.
- Oh, my God. What happened?
(Leonard:)Well, your ex-boyfriend sends his regards
and I think the rest is fairly self-explanatory.
(Penny:)I'm so sorry.
(Penny:)I really thought if you guys went
instead of me he wouldn't be such an ass.
(Leonard:)No, it was a valid hypothesis.
That was a valid hypo...?
What is happening to you?
(Penny:)Really, thank you so much
for going and trying.
You just... You're so terrific.
(Penny:)Why don't you put some clothes on,
I'll get my purse, and dinner is on me, okay?
- Really? Great.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)Okay.